<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Digicardz</string>
    <string name="array">Contact</string>
    <string name="desc">SK AI Technologies and Solutions (SKAITAS) has opened a new realm of possibilities where one can share information without relying on the old fashioned way. Tired of constantly telling your contact number, email address to others? Worry no more, SKAITAS is here to ease your future. Introducing the eco-friendly and digitalized cards of the future, Digi-Cardz. Digi-Cardz bring a futuristic approach to the conventional means of information distribution. All of your information and means to contact will be a single click away. Digi-Cardz are fully customizable and can cater to all of your needs. Just by tapping on the various featured icons, people can save your contact, call you, find you on social networks or find your business/personal location.</string>
    <string name="hometxt"><![CDATA[SK AI Technologies & Solutions (SKAITAS) has opened a new realm of possibilities where one can share information without relying on the old fashioned way. Tired of constantly telling your contact number, email address to others? Worry no more, SKAITAS is here to ease your future.]]></string>
    <string name="offer">Launch Offer 10% Discount on Product Price</string>
    <string name="pre_defined_design">Pre Defined Design</string>
    <string name="logo_should_be_provided_if_user_wants_us_to_make_the_logo_extra_charges_will_be_applied">* Logo should be provided. If user wants us to make the logo, extra charges will be applied.</string>
    <string name="qr_download_functionality_can_be_added_to_basic_and_pro_plans_as_well_at_a_fee_of_250_max_size_25mb">* QR / Download functionality can be added to Basic and Pro Plans as well at a fee of ₹ 250 (Max size - 25MB).</string>
    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item>Select Subject</item>
        <item>Job Queries</item>
        <item>Our Services</item>
        <item>For Partnership</item>
        <item>Review</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="packagetype">
        <item>Basic</item>
        <item>Pro</item>
        <item>Premium</item>
        <item>Ultimate</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="d1colorpattern">
        <item>Black Shade</item>
        <item>Purple Shade</item>
        <item>Green Shade</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>